### Contact

Raleigh NC 27612 toufikaminew@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/taoufika (LinkedIn)

Ibladma.github.io/React-Portfolio/ (Portfolio) github.com/Ibladma (Portfolio)

## Top Skills

**Programming** 

Cybersecurity

Full-Stack Development

## Languages

French (Native or Bilingual)

Python (Limited Working)

HTML (Professional Working)

English (Native or Bilingual)

CSS (Professional Working)

Arabic (Native or Bilingual)

Spanish (Elementary)

Javascript (Elementary)

#### Certifications

Giving Your Elevator Pitch

CompTIA A+ (220-1001) Cert Prep 6: Physical Networking

CompTIA CySA+ (CS0-002) Cert Prep: 1 Threat Management

Programming Foundations: Web

Security

Build a Full-Stack JavaScript Application Using AWS Amplify

# **Taoufik Ammi**

Full Stack Web Developer, System Admin and an aspiring CyberSecurity enthusiast. Currently transferring my IT experience and skills towards specializing in Software Development and Cybersecurity

Raleigh

# Summary

Full Stack Web Developer and an aspiring CyberSecurity professional with a Computer Science BA degree, and 10+ years experience working in IT as a senior computer engineer, system admin by day, and web designer by night which helped me accumulate couple of years experience working as a freelancer web designer.

Currently transferring my extensive IT experience and knowledge towards specializing in Web Development and Cybersecurity thru pursuing Security+ Cert and completing the Cybersecurity Bootcamp at Springboard."

# Experience

HCL Technologies
Senior Information Technology Specialist
March 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Freelancer.com
Freelance Web Designer
January 2020 - Present (2 years)

Tenet Healthcare
Taleo HealthStream Tier II Remote Support Specialist
August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

Dallas, Texas, United States

NEC Corporation Level 2 Support Technician October 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Pei Wei

Tier III Restaurant Support Analyst January 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 4 months)

Brinker International
Client Support Professional
January 2017 - January 2018 (1 year 1 month)

D&H Distributing
Cloud Client Support Professional
January 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 5 months)

EarthLink Internet
Desktop Support Engineer
January 2012 - January 2016 (4 years 1 month)

### Education

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Full Stack dev · (June 2021 - November 2021)

Springboard

Cyber Security · (May 2021 - April 2022)

Franklin University
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology Project
Management · (2009 - 2013)

The Ohio State University
Associate's degree, Information Technology (2007 - 2009)